We're free at last! Yeah!
Next up is Kaido! Kick. His. Ass!
Kick. His. Ass!
Luffy!
You gotta be careful! Hey!
So about Kaido, got a plan?
You wanna team up with me?
Get bent you saw what he did to
my partner I want revenge myself.
Be grateful I don't finish you
off right now like I should.
I can't trust anyone
alliances are a waste of time.
Go, go, go, go!
Come on, killer.
It's time for us to get our crew back.
Screw Straw Hat.
We'll handle things our way.
Bluers the horizon.
We will find infinity for sure!
Let's sail for this blue
sea and let the wind.
Take us far away.
Don't give up.
So I can come back to this moment.
So I can be present right here.
Throw away this drop.
Sometimes we share.
Shut it up, do not be
so afraid to find us.
To have a friend right here.
And I will always be here by your side.
To take care of you.
Even in the darkest of times I'll try.
Looking brave, it's alright.
Cause we are the ones who
are meant to move them up.
We will move to a rushing horizon.
We will find insanity for sure.
We will step ahead, we will win for sure.
Dreaming on, we will
move towards the horizon.
We will fight however we can.
In order to be the best, we will run.
To the top, to the end.
We gotta be the ones that
just keep dreaming on.
I just can't give up now.
I can never stop cause.
I gotta give everything I got to.
Become the greatest of all times.
We will move towards the horizon.
We will find infinity for sure.
We will step back.
Then we will reach for sure.
Don't keep moving on?
The toll of 20 years.
How can I hold on to such a hopeful
dream when we've lost so much?
Ten years was as much
indignity as they could stand.
When they'd suffered enough, they
raided Onigashima and all perished.
What in the world happened here?
It's been ten years already.
We grow older by the day.
If we wait another ten
years, we'll be even weaker.
And what do we do if the people
we're waiting for don't come back?
Just trust in Lady Toki.
Mark my words, all of you,
our comrades, will return.
And Lord Momonosuke will be with them.
How much longer can we oppose Orochi?
We're so hungry!
Starvation will kill us before any battle!
Kaido's army is here!
That was our only will!
I don't care!
We still have some life in us.
Please let us take action!
I forbid it.
You'll march to your deaths?
Unless we all unite under the
Kozuki banner, we'll fail!
I can't take anymore!
I'm so sorry!
We beg of you.
At least let us die a samurai's death.
It's all we ask.
To pass with the Cotton in hand.
Don't stand in our way!
We had a word when we were little.
We would test our mettle
with how loud we could yell.
When people value themselves too
highly, they stop taking risks.
Unachi!
Surrender your name and be as a child.
Clear your mind and take the leap!
That was our battle cry!
Raise your voice and be heard! Tsunachi!
Tsunachi! Tsunachi! Tsunachi!
Stop this!
I don't know.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Shulaji!
Shulaji! Shulaji!
At least let us die a samurai death.
Oh,
my God.
Tsunachi!
Why did we all have to
suffer this pain for
20 long years we'll know
once the job is done?
Surely there is a deeper
meaning I have no reason
to doubt Lord Odin listen
we've got a new goal
Eight days from now is the
fire festival in the name of
Kozuki Odin we'll raid Onigashima
Seek out the pirate invaders!
Drag Orochi and Kaido out
of hiding and kill them!
If you still have the metal to fight
back, then rise up and follow me!
Count us in, Chief!
It's about time we wreck those guys!
Oh, shut us back.
It's clear you haven't
changed at all, Kin'emon.
We may have been the
same age back in the day.
But keep in mind, we're now 20
years stronger than you, young 'un.
Tell him, doggy.
You, Kara, make a good point.
Quiet, old-timers.
You better not slow us down. Huh?
Quiet, you young pup.
Whoa, calm down, you guys.
None of us are equipped to
break up an Akazaya quarrel.
They're what?
So the Straw Hat guy is
a pirate, same as Kaido?
Not the same at all.
Then we can't trust him.
He'll just stab us right in the back.
Why would you bring one of
his kind to help anyway, huh?
The seas are vast, and not all
pirates have ill intent, sir.
That gentleman's involvement is crucial
in our plans to overthrow Kaido.
How can you expect us to trust him?
You've got some convincing to do.
Oh, dear.
I need something more to persuade them.
Although, it seems they
come to their senses.
Is it true that you traveled
here from 20 years in the past?
Tell us! Race,
you always looked a lot
older than you really were,
so it's hard to tell if
you've actually aged or not.
I know you didn't intend to be
hurtful, but come now! Did Mr.
Strawhead just wander off?
Tom, it's too dangerous.
You really shouldn't be here.
I'm sorry, Big Bro.
I was worried.
But I'm really happy
that you're still okay!
Yeah.
Okay?
He's barely alive. Huh?
Where does it hurt?
Let me help you.
Don't touch him.
I'm trying to find an antibody right now.
Why did you show up when you
knew this would fall on me?
I would say that you deserved it, but I
can see that you're clearly suffering.
Zero, apologize.
I'm sorry.
It's painful.
Please help me. One sec.
You don't need a pirate.
Help me.
Luffy is extraordinary,
even if he is foolish.
I could never do such a thing.
Oh, you know why?
Because you're an idiot.
You're a Secret cat, and
weak as hell, and a wimp.
You're just a big baby.
Silence, insolent dog!
You have no right to address
me in such a fashion!
Mama, please don't punch him!
Are you chickening out on me?
Come fight me!
Step aside!
I am Odin's son!
I possess every right to
be Shogun of this land!
Do something about it, prove it!
We don't want them here.
Go on, Momo!
Stop that! You're crazy! You'll kill me!
Do I have to spill it out, dummy?
They're waiting for you!
Ahh!
YES!
Ahhh!
Ahh!
Aah! Ahh! Ahh!
Impossible.
Could it be?
Lord Momonosuke is here.
You're still alive!
I can't believe it.
I see now.
It's not the promise That we were lacking.
But a dream.
A driving force that
lies Beyond the battle?
I've accomplished nothing.
What they see is not myself,
but the memory of my father.
The great shadow cast by him that
protected the land of Wano long ago.
I...
I cannot do this.
Look, it's too much.
I want to vanquish Everikido!
Momonosuke, you mustn't
be afraid. Breathe.
You must be strong.
You are a lord.
Attention!
Please hear me out!
I shall speak to you of the
journey I have undertook.
After arriving in the present,
I sent out with Kin'emon and
the others in search of allies.
However, we were struck
with tragedy and separated.
I found myself in a dangerous
place with no hope of escape.
I faced many trials, and if not for
the aid of Luffy and his comrades,
I surely would not be
standing here before you.
I know I may be weak and lack experience,
but I will avenge my family and the
land of Wano, no matter what it takes.
even in my darkest hour i was
able to carry on because i held on
to one dear thing a dream my goal
is clear i must find like-minded
allies my countrymen you are the
people who support i need more than
ever the people of this land every
one of us shares the same desire
Take back our home!
The land of Wano!
I know you've suffered greatly,
waiting for all these years!
So I thank you with all of
my heart for your faith!
I am heir to Lord Odin,
daimyo of this country!
I am Kozuki Momonosuke!
It's time!
Let us rise up!
It warms my heart to see Lord Momonosuke
taking charge so boldly. Forgive me.
I must take leave for now.
But you have my word I shall rejoin you
before the battle. Very well. Understood.
Oh,
my
God.
Are we finally done with this?
I've got too many damn ninjas.
Pain in my ass.
Zoro-Judo, are you injured?
I'm fine.
Forgive me.
I've become a burden.
It's no trouble.
Well, maybe a bit.
But if you got killed, I'd never be
able to show my face to Momonosuke.
So where do we head next?
That house in the snow, right?
I just need a good hiding place.
The location doesn't really matter.
We need to track down that
guy who stole my sword.
I can guide you to him easily.
He's always at Bandit's Bridge in Ringo.
I have to get it back before the big raid.
I don't feel comfortable without it.
I must have really pissed off Oduchi, huh?
He's pulling out all the
stops to hunt us down.
Poor Otaku.
I hope she's alright.
Yasui!
I'm coming!
After having to witness
such a horrible scene,
I wish I'd been able to stay by her side.
You can work that out when you see her.
My friends will keep her safe.
Don't worry, okay?
Orji will pay for what he did.
I'll avenge Tonoyasu at any cost.
I wish I was strong, if I had the
power, I would kill him myself.
What did you say?!
You mean you let those
loathsome traitors escape?!
And what of that savage
Ronin who attacked me?!
I...
I failed you, my lord.
Do you have any more bad news, Will?
No, good news!
We captured a man named Trafalgar!
Huh? Say again?
Trafal-what?
Who in the hell is that?!
He's an enemy intruder
just like straw had now we
have two of their masterminds
under our control.
They're helpless What
are you doing with him?
For pirates betrayal never
goes out of style right now.
We're putting that to use
We'll torture him first, but we'll
find other uses for him, too.
That is good news and what of the
capital have you quelled the riots yet?
It's all under control local
forces are on high alert samurai
and ninja are on patrol as we
speak combing every street and
establishment in town it's only a
matter of time until the intruders
are caught while we're settling
that I promise we'll keep you safe.
If you see any of these criminals,
you must report it immediately!
Wow, there's so many!
A lot of bad guys on the loose!
It's treason to aid them in any way, and
allowing them to escape is a crime as well!
So take heed!
Well, that sucks.
Guess we're clearing out
of the capital for now.
We're not just wanted here.
Now it's the entire country!
Orochi's network of assassins will be on
the lookout for us, ready for a fight.
After all, our objective was to
find allies with the Moon Tattoo.
Seems like kind of an
empty victory, though.
You're right.
Unless we can free them.
We're not criminals! Let us go!
Sit down and shut up!
I thought Toniyasu's speech
would have done the trick.
So now they're just keeping them
locked up for the hell of it?
Well, it might be
something like that, yes?
There must be a thousand or so
rebels in the prisoners' quarters,
suffering the whims of Orochi.
Hey, shouldn't they have
set these guys free by now?
How would that work?
Lord Orochi says, I goofed up?
We can't expect the Shogun
to admit he was wrong.
That's a good point.
These people have proven
themselves to be our allies.
We need them, and beyond
that, we owe them our aid.
Law's buddies must be
stuck in there too, huh?
Hey, Shinobu, what are those people doing?
Oh, they're preparing skyboats.
What are they for?
Skyboats are an important
part of the fire festival.
Two beloved figures just died.
They must not feel like celebrating.
Actually, it's just the opposite.
The Fire Festival is an event to honor
friends and family who have passed away.
And the bigger the celebration, the more
likely your thoughts will reach the dead.
I see.
Sounds like they'd better
party pretty hard then.
You made it that's great.
Yeah.
Sorry to worry you.
That was a real mess.
I didn't catch the details.
But I heard you got caught.
Luckily we escaped.
Oh.
All right.
Take a look at this.
It's from that time.
Yasuie. Huh?
He gave you this?
He drew that symbol and showed
it to the people with the tattoos
before he died. Hmm.
There's something different.
It looks like he added
two lines to the snake?
Yeah, you got it.
He changed the meaning,
but I don't know how.
Seemed to work out, though.
What I mean is the people
from Wano understood it.
It was Yosui's final message to them.
This is kind of a big deal.
I'll show Kin'emon.
He'll know what to do.
Thank you, Nami.
Better get going, then!
If you need help, come to
Amigasa Village, kay? Thanks.
When you see your friends,
tell them we said hi!
Captain.
Captain!
We made a bargain and
your lives were the chips.
Our lives? What?
This sounds like a trap!
It's quite straightforward.
If I refuse to release you, Then
your captain will take my life.
Which is to say, he'll take yours as well.
Never betting on tomorrow, he'll make
any sacrifice without a second thought.
I'm afraid that I must take
his threat very seriously.
Captain, I'm sorry!
We blew it, didn't we?
These are your lives.
I'm returning them to you.
I hold no power over them,
and they're free to leave.
I trust this meets your
conditions, Trafalgar.
Our lives aren't worth it! Captain!
Don't go!
Be quiet and listen.
Don't tell the Straw Hats I was caught.
If anyone asks questions,
just say you escaped.
I don't get it! Captain!
Don't do this!
Come back!
It's not worth it!
Captain!
It's our fault!
And now, who knows what our captain
is going through with their clutches!
We can't just sit around and wait!
As the Heart Pirates, we have a job to do!
We'll save our captain
no matter what it takes!
Kittymon's plan will have to wait!
I will not let our captain die!
I have had enough of you, Law.
Give it up already.
I think you need to
step away for a moment.
You've been acting out of sorts ever
since we began this interrogation.
Whatever.
Don't overthink it.
Let's just get this over with.
Of course, it shouldn't
take long after all.
We don't need this
unpleasantness to drag on.
We know you're connected to
Straw Hat, so start talking.
Why have you come to the land of Wano?
What are you plotting?
I want every last detail.
Wow.